But over here, I'm looking for an option. Yeah, use microphone. So I wanted to show you this one as well
So as you saw, I just typed my command, right, but I also can
Start talking and Google will or Gemini will convert what I said into text. So I can click use microphone over here
and I allow this time
Sorry, you're using the wrong microphone, right?
So I wanted to be this one. Yes, it's recording my voice now and I click use microphone
Hello Gemini today. I decided
Okay, so
What happened again?
Hello Gemini today, I decided to drink my coffee outside and I leave in Lyon, France
So I want you to give me your top suggestions on where I should drink my coffee. Thank you so much
And by clicking again the microphone mode will be off and as you see I have my command ready over here
So it says hello Gemini today. I decided to blah, blah, blah, right?